hello
everybody I just wanted to on
impulse make a little video just to say
hello before the new year comes I am out
here in the forest it is so quiet and
magical and it is snowing out and I just
I feel like I've been transported to
Narnia and so I just wanted to take this
opportunity to just say hello before we
come into the new year which is just
around the corner and I know for a lot
of us the New Year means New Beginnings
sometimes new goals things we're trying
to do for me something really helpful I
found has been not so much asking what I
need to add in to my life and perhaps
instead what I need to take out if we
are truly open to it and we know what it
is we need to thrive and heal I think
there often are at least a few things we
can do to simplify our days and find a
little more slowness I'm going to be
finding myself faced with huge Life
Changes next year and I have slowly
slowly turned into someone who has come
to really Embrace those changes and as
many of you know if you've been on this
channel for a long time you have seen me
through the final steps of recovery from
an eating disorder also dealing with
connected to that a lot of anxiety and a
tenden to be a very sensitive very
easily overwhelmed person a huge part of
the process of learning to live with
myself and Thrive has been to not be
afraid of the feelings that arise that
make me uncomfortable to sit and be
still and ask myself why why do I feel a
need to assert a unrealistic sense of
control over my life we are only here
for a very short amount of time and I
think once you really sit with that you
really accept your mortality you accept
the beauty of the life cycle and how it
Gives Life Meaning you realize you don't
want to waste any more time living in
fear living afraid of your own emotions
trying to avoid or suppress parts of who
you are so you can start to nurture
yourself and find who it is you were
meant to be all along and to really
nurture that soul I wanted to just wish
you the very best and please comment
down below any wisdom or anything you've
learned from this year that you're going
to be bringing into the next and
hopefully we can face the new year
together I think it is all about love at
the end of the day isn't it at least it
is for me so though I am imperfect and
I've made many mistakes I really
appreciate sharing this platform with
all of you you have made it such a cozy
loving space and I'm looking forward to
hopefully giving you some updates along
the way as I enter this new era of
Parenthood
so much to think about so much to do so
much to discover I'm wishing you all a
wonderful New Year and I will see you
very soon goodbye hi come here come here
buddy come
[Music]
here